{
    "topic": "Software Design",
    "Subject": "Software Engineering",
    "data": [
        {
            "question": "An ER diagram depicts :",
            "op1": "Entities",
            "op2": "Keys",
            "op3": "Relationship",
            "op4": "All of these above",
            "answer:": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "In an ER diagram noun is treated as :",
            "op1": "Entity",
            "op2": "Relationship",
            "op3": "Primary key",
            "op4": "Foreign key",
            "answer:": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Data Flow Diagrams are used for :",
            "op1": "Process modelling",
            "op2": "Modelling interactions in a real time environment",
            "op3": "Data modelling",
            "op4": "None of these above",
            "answer:": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Requirements to develop a software :",
            "op1": "Model business",
            "op2": "Analyze",
            "op3": "Design",
            "op4": "All of these above",
            "answer:": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "The basic tool used in structured design is a :",
            "op1": "Structure Chart",
            "op2": "Data flow diagram",
            "op3": "ER diagram",
            "op4": "Program flowchart",
            "answer:": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "At highest level, a DFD is referred to as :",
            "op1": "Scope diagram",
            "op2": "Context diagram",
            "op3": "Level 1 DFD",
            "op4": "Level 2 F",
            "answer:": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "In a DFD, an originator or data receiver is usually designated by",
            "op1": "square box",
            "op2": "A circle",
            "op3": "A rectangle",
            "op4": "None of these",
            "answer:": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "ER diagram is related with :",
            "op1": "Entity relationship",
            "op2": "Data flow",
            "op3": "Foreign key",
            "op4": "System testing",
            "answer:": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The output of System Design stage is represented by",
            "op1": "State diagram",
            "op2": "Structure chart",
            "op3": "ER diagram",
            "op4": "Context diagram",
            "answer:": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "A Zero level DFD describes :",
            "op1": "The fully blown up System Design",
            "op2": "Data flow in all the modules",
            "op3": "Overview of processes, inputs and output",
            "op4": "None of these",
            "answer:": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "The database design activity deals with the design of the",
            "op1": "Logical database",
            "op2": "Physical database",
            "op3": "Both [A] and [B]",
            "op4": "Only [B]",
            "answer:": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "At the most detailed level of the Data flow diagram involves which one of following process ?",
            "op1": "Functional primitives",
            "op2": "Data flows",
            "op3": "Interfaces",
            "op4": "Transform descriptions",
            "answer:": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following defines the rules of DFD ?",
            "op1": "ll data flows must contain data",
            "op2": "All data flows must begin and/or end at a process",
            "op3": "Only processes can connect to data storages",
            "op4": "All of the above",
            "answer:": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Which one of the following is not related to DFD ?",
            "op1": "Bubble (Process)",
            "op2": "Arrow (Flow)",
            "op3": "Secondary storage",
            "op4": "ata store",
            "answer:": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Entities, attributes and relationships are associated with",
            "op1": "logical concepts of data",
            "op2": "physical concepts of data",
            "op3": "programming",
            "op4": "none of these",
            "answer:": 1
        }
    ]
}